PRINCEWILL UZOCHUKWU DURU

09034031589

duruprincewilluzochukwu@gmail.com

No 6, Ijoola Street, Maryland, Ikeja, Lagos State https://princewillduru.netlify.app/

EDUCATION

| Rufus Giwa Polytechnic, Owo, Ondo State | 2017 – 2019 |
|---|-------------|
| HND In Estate Management and Valuation | |
| Rufus Giwa Polytechnic, Owo, Ondo State | 2014 – 2016 |
| OND In Estate Management and Valuation | |
| High Focus International School | 2007 – 2013 |
| Secondary School Certificate (WAEC) | |

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am a passionate, self-motivated learner with a keen interest in working in a growing technological firm where I can contribute to its growth and create operative systems for efficiency purposes.

SUMMARY

Creative Front End Developer with 2 years of experience in building and maintaining web applications. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, using modern library such as REACTJS.

Understanding in the integration of backend Javascript library such NODEJS.

Excellent team player with global mindset.

Good interpersonal skills to build good working relationship.

Good communication skill.

WORK EXPERIENCE

WillTrip | Hotel/Travel Booking Application

2022

- Created the interface of the web application.
- Worked to give the web application a great user friendly web pages and user experience.
- Managed user data.
- Fetched Hotels, Restaurants and Attraction centers data from a backend API to respond to users requesnt.

LilsenFoods | minimalist e-commerce Food ordering Application

2021

- Created the interface of the web application.
- Worked to give the web application a great user friendly web pages and user experience.
- Managed user data.
- Created the option of manually requesting for a preferred food.
- Managed user request.

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT AND CERTIFICATIONS

FreeCodeCamp
Responsive Web Design
FreeCodeCamp
JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

Aug 2021

Nov 2021

LEADERSHIP

President 2019-2019

Estate Management and Valuation Department (EMSA), Rufus Giwa Polytechnic Chapter

- Facilitate, promote and negotiate good welfare for the students
- Organize meetings with the head of the department on issues regarding the department
- Managed and executed projects for the department.

Community Development Coordinator

2021-2022

National Youth Service Corps, Itesiwaju, Oyo State

- Organized the community development service for the community
- Worked with the Local Government Inspector and community heads on issues relating to the communities' development
- Facilitated, promoted, and negotiated community development projects
- Planned and monitored empowerment programs.

SKILLS & HOBBIES

Technical skills: Vast knowledge in the use of Front-end technologies such as HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Tailwindcss, Reactjs, Nodejs and Redux.

Organizational Skills: Creative thinking, Problem Solving, Excellent Communication, and Team Management.

Hobbies: Playing video games, Gymnastics, and sports.

REFERENCES

Mr. Falona. K.

Lecturer, Department of Estate Management and Valuation, Akure, Ondo State. 08066154327

Mr. Omale

Life Press, Lagos State 08158190071